Lycanthrope?
Lycanthropes are those who
carry the blood of Vargr,
the wolf god of the ancient Vargr Kingdom.
You are a werewolf chosen by a god.
As you know, werewolves have inherited
that blood for generations,
and the status and traditions
that come with it.
Those who wear that necklace,
Silver Fang, have the power
to lead a pack.
They are great warriors.
True Lycanthropes.
It's only old folks like me
who know that now.
But you must feel that you're
different from your kin somehow.
Everyone else naturally becomes a wolf
under the light of the full moon,
so why not me?
Am I defective after all?
You're different from your kin
because you were born to lead us.
Be careful. You're the one they're after.
Dardan's capturing every
werewolf he can
in order to acquire the blood
of Vargr in your veins.
Some of our kin have been
hurt or even killed.
Because of me?
Damn it!
They'll pay for this!
You said the others
were taken to Automnal.
Yes.
Kamil and the others must be there—
I swear I'll save our brothers.
Sir, please tell us everything
you can that might help us.
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- Mortal Combat in Automnal -
You still haven't found one?!
I'm sorry. There wasn't one
among the recently captured—
Keep looking!
Dardan!
Release the princess this instant.
It's not too late.
What you're trying to do is unforgivable.
Is this about status again?
No. It's a matter of disposition.
That power wasn't passed down to
those born into the royal family.
It was passed to those
with the right disposition.
The royal family has
merely protected that.
You aren't worthy.
Even if you were born a royal,
a selfish man like you who sacrifices
others could never acquire that power.
You won't be able to talk
down to me for much longer.
There's nothing you can do now.
I'll prove that I was right,
both back then and now.
What's wrong with this city?
It's so lifeless.
All the residents are vampires.
But no one's attacking us.
Don't make eye contact.
So the whole city is
under Dardan's control?
We're surrounded by enemies.
Right now, finding the sword comes first.
Looks like the museum's under city hall.
Welcome to the Automnal Public Museum.
I am Trisha, the curator. This way.
Be careful, guys.
She's no ordinary vampire.
In here. This is where the ancient
furnishings are on display.
Feel free to look around.
I found it!
Can we take it with us?
I'll try.
So you came for that after all.
You won't be taking that sword.
All of you will die here.
Heli, take the sword
while she's distracted!
What is this? My hands
are moving on their own!
Heli!
Wh-What's happening?
My hands...
My body...
I can't move!
That sword may be fearsome, but what
matters is which way it's pointing.
And I can control which way it points.
This time, you'll kill your friends with
the blade you used to slaughter my kin!
If I don't break free of her control,
I'll cut down all of my friends.
Damn. I can't move my own body!
Is she controlling all
seven of us by herself?
Shion, can't you do anything?!
I can hypnotize people, too!
Shion!
Stop!
Noa...
You're wasting your time.
Noa!
My body's moving on its own!
Jaan!
Sol...
Solon!
Now everything will be mine.
This is just like back then.
Solon...
Why is this happening?
Noa!
Damn!
What should we do?
I love the looks on your faces.
I wish I could share this with someone.
Don't worry. I won't let
you die that easily.
It'd be a waste to end the fun so—
Damn it! You'll pay for that!
Jino!
How does it feel to kill each other?
You poor thing.
That was the perfect chance.
Damn it!
This ends now!
Jakah...
There's only one left.
Off with his head!
Jaan...
You dare to defy me? How insolent!
Why, you...
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Stop!
Tch. You just won't give up.
Damn you!
Damn. Too shallow.
I've lost too much blood.
I'm too slow.
Jakah!
My wound is closing.
Is this Sooha's power?
But the others...
This isn't good.
I have to finish this quickly.
That old man said the ship transporting
our kind was going to Automnal, right?
Yeah.
The harbor's over there.
Wait!
What is it, Tahel?
Did you find something?
It's faint, but I smell
our brothers over there.
I can move.
Taking damage has weakened
her control considerably.
She can't control all seven
of us at once after all.
She can only fully control one person.
She can only stop the
other six from moving.
And now, she can't even fully control one.
Which means she's running out of steam.
Don't move!
Now!
Trena!
It can't be...
There's another one?
You'll pay for what you've done to Trisha.
I'll make sure of that.
Trisha stops your movements,
and I cut off your heads.
In other words, you can't beat us!
Jaan!
Jakah!
Shion!
How?
Don't bother!
You're the last one.
I'll take your head off
with a single swing!
Stop!
Sooha...
Sooha?!
Trisha!
Trisha...
No...
You bit me.
If you die...
Sooha!
Where is she? Did I imagine that?
She was here a moment ago.
No, I'd recognize her anywhere.
Sooha, are you okay?!
To the woods.
The woods?
When the full moon rises,
the ritual will begin.
Before that happens,
go to the Hivernal Woods.
Before Dardan takes my power. Hurry!
Sooha.
That was undoubtedly the
princess's misty form ability.
She used it then, too.
Your Highness. Your Highness!
Has her true power awoken?
But she shouldn't have full use of it yet.
Eventually, they'll all
become mine anyway.
Lord Dardan.
What is it?
We've found a Lycanthrope.
Sooha came here?
Yeah.
She suddenly appeared and vanished?
I think that was her power.
Sooha told me
she's currently trapped on the
moon altar in the Hivernal Woods.
Hivernal Woods?
Wait.
It's here.
The ritual will be held
when the full moon rises.
We have to save Sooha before then,
or Dardan will take her power.
What?
The full moon? But that's tonight!
Can you guys do it?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Of course we can.
Because of me, you—
If we don't hurry, the moon's gonna rise.
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
There are corpses everywhere.
What happened here?
It's probably because those sisters died.
These must be the low-ranking
vampires they bit.
It all started with Dardan,
the First Vampire.
If we defeat him, all the vampires
he created will be destroyed.
Where are our kin?
I-I was just asked to...
I can't breathe...
You're holding the werewolves
here somewhere, aren't you?
Hand over the key.
Kamil! Ruslan!
Khan! Guys!
I'm so glad!
Mahan, you're okay.
Sorry we took so long.
Are you two hurt?
We're fine.
We had chances to escape, but we
stayed to find out what's going on.
Sorry for making you worry.
It's fine. We're just glad you're okay.
Where are the others?
They were taken somewhere else.
What?!
To someplace called the moon altar.
The moon altar?
We heard it's in the woods nearby.
Okay. Let's go.
You...
I finally found you, Lycanthrope.
Next time, Episode 11:
"Hazy Moon: Vargr's Blood."
- Vargr's Blood -